datanumen.com 2017-02-08

# DataNumen: Privacy Policy

|  |  |  |  |   
---|---|---|---|---  
|  |  |  |   
  |  |    
  |   |   |   |    
  |  |  |  | 

**Privacy Policy**

|    
---|---|---  

| 

DataNumen, Inc. is committed to maintaining the privacy of the information you share with us. We will never sell, distribute, or rent information about you and your purchases at DataNumen, Inc.. We will only use the information you share with us for the purposes of enhancing your use of our web site, products, services, or, with your permission, sending you information about our products and services. 

Please take a moment to read our privacy policy for a better understanding of the measures we take to protect you and the information you share with us. If you don't find your concern addressed here, please feel free to contact us . 

This privacy policy will explain the following regarding our collection of information:   
  
---  
| 

**The information we collect.**  
  
|   |  | 

Whenever you shop our online store, at the time of check-out, we obtain the information we need from you to complete your transaction. To process your order, we require you to supply us with your correct billing, shipping and contact information. The transfer of this information is secure and cannot be received or read by others.  
  
---|---|---  
  |  | 

When you send emails to us asking questions on our website, products, services, or your purchases with us, we obtain the information we need from you to answer your questions appropriately.   
  
  |  | 

When we provide technical supports to you, if necessary, we may collect corrupt data files from you via email or ftp, in order to help you solve the problems in using our products.   

| 

**How we use the information we collect.**  
  
|   |  | 

**Online Orders**  
We use the personal information you supply when placing an online order to complete and ship your order. Your email address is used to send you an order confirmation, the registration information, as well as to alert you to any changes in the availability of the items you ordered.   
  
---|---|---  
  |  | 

**Technical Support**  
We use the personal information you supply when you submit a support question to respond to your question. Your email address is used to send a response from our Technical Support team.   
  
  |  | 

**Data Files**  
Our email and ftp servers are highly protected so that only our engineers can retrieve files from them. We never transmit your data files via email or ftp unless encrypted with very strong algorithms. Your data files are securely deleted from our servers within 72 Hours automatically.   

| 

**How to gain access to the information we have on file for you**  
  
There may be times where you wish to gain access to the information we have on file for you. To receive a copy of this information, please contact us .   

| **Notification of changes**  
  
If, at some point in the future, there is a change to our privacy policy and/or practices that affect your personally identifiable information, we will notify you by email of the relevant changes.
